Boldizsar Banfia

Software Engineer Student

07341043492 | boldizsar.banfiaagmail.com | LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/banfia-boldizsar-b1a1971bb/

Statement

A persistent bubbly software engineer student eager to break into developing production. I am inquisitive in nature, and relish the rewarding feeling of solving a problem whether in a team or individually. 14 years of work experience across various industries, taught me how to take ownership of challenges and be goal orientated and willing to go the extra mile.

Work Experience

2022 - Present | Controller, Boarhunt Recovery

- > Managing a small team
- > Allocating jobs, handling calls and emails

2021 - 2022 | Delivery Driver, Tesco

< Delivering items to clients in a safe, timely
manner</pre>

2018 - 2021 | Health Care Assistant, ST Magnus Hospital

- >Delivering quality care support on a low security unit
- > Acquired level 3 diploma

2015 - 2017 | Croupier, Las Vegas Casino

> Supervising hand-played games

Skills

> Languages: HTML, CSS, JAVA, jQuery, JAVASCRIPT with Node,

SQL, Python, MongoDB

> Libraries: Mongoose, Ajax,
matplotlib

- > CCNA Network and Security
- > Proven Quick learner, organised and quick to adapt
- > Humble and curious
- > Can do attitude

Education

2019- B.Sc. Software Engineering Solent University Southampton

- > Foundational and first year finished with 2:1.
- > Expected second year outcome likewise 2:1
- -

References

Available upon request